The next thing that has been so frustrating that nothing has built in here
Has been in real plywood but it is the construction plywood
that has to make concrete castings.
That is what is available.
They are oblique and wind and large holes in all this.
Regular carpentry plywood is not available
And the prices we should not talk about.
The absurd is that it has not been easy to get hold
in the right material for construction.
The seat bench will of course be dressed and then I will
Have the same wooden floor as I have.
But on Youtube I have seen a lot that do tests, stealing it
And just mount the firm pointing straight up.
And does it go as I hope they do, then it is perfect
Because then I will fold it directly into the spoiler.
But I also want to see how much difference it will be at the download speed.
Is it negligible then I will stel operate it
and has a great impact.
So when I drive loosely with my foot.
You know this should work in the main.
But I don't know.
That's the fun.
It will do during the journey instead.
So I have like mini projects
Which I can grab when I feel it.
Rainy days.
When it is rainy and windy then you stand in there and paint?
Exactly, some things that I will take with me on the trip.
It won't be so fun to sleep in it then.
You have to be a morning girl and then you have to be out for the rest of the day.
So when it doesn't rain, then you have to do it.
So it must be.
It is great to see that it is moving forward here.
It is making progress.
Next time we see I have much more surface layer in place
So it will look like it has happened much more outside it.